The Revenge of Jennifer Hills.
I Spit on Your Grave is a thriller, crime, horror
film directed by Steven R. Monroe.
A beautiful woman from the city, Jennifer Hills, rents an isolated
cabin in the country to write her latest novel.
Soon, a group of local lowlifes subject her to a
nightmare of degradation, rape, and violence.
Jennifer Hills, played by Sarah Butler.
John 'Johnny' Miller, played by Jeff Branson.
Earl, played by Tracey Walter.
Sheriff Storch, played by Andrew Howard.
Matthew, played by Chad Lindberg.
Andy, played by Rodney Eastman.
I Spit on Your Grave is a 2010 American rape and revenge horror film and a remake of the
controversial 1978 cult film of the same name (originally titled Day of the Woman).
It was directed by Steven R.
Monroe and written by Stuart Morse, based on the original film's director/writer Meir Zarchi's screenplay, and stars Sarah
Butler, Jeff Branson, Daniel Franzese, Rodney Eastman, Chad Lindberg, Tracey Walter, and Andrew Howard.
It was distributed by CineTel, and produced by the
company's president and CEO Paul Hertzberg.
Lisa Hansen, Jeff Klein, Alan Ostroff, Gary Needle, and Meir Zarchi
(director of the original) served as executive producers.
Principal photography began on November 2, 2009, with
location filming taking place in Louisiana.
I Spit on Your Grave had its premiere on Texas Frightmare Weekend on May 1, 2010, and was
theatrically released in the United States on October 8, 2010, by Anchor Bay.
The film received negative reviews from critics and
grossed $572,809 on a $2 million budget.
The film was followed by two sequels, I Spit on Your Grave 2 (2013)
and I Spit on Your Grave III: Vengeance Is Mine (2015).
The film explores themes of rape, fondling, remake, revenge, writer.
The tone is dark and intense.